Mertkan Tecer

G-43. Sokak, Istanbul, İstanbul mertkan.tecer@gmail.com +(90) 546 964 93 44

Summary

I was born in June 5th 1998. I graduated my high school from Bakırköy Anadolu Ticaret Meslek Lisesi in between 2012-2016.

I graduated my collage from Istanbul University Computer Programming department in 2018.

I studied at Anadolu University Computer Education and Instructional Technologies department.

My Job experiences and more details on below.

Experience

İstanbul Elektrik Tramvay ve Tünel İşletmeleri

Data Management Intern • İstanbul, Beyoğlu

09/2015 - 07/2016

Seyhan Müzik

Front End Developer Intern • İstanbul, Unkapanı

06/2017 - 07/2017

Sekompos A.ş

Front End Developer Intern • İstanbul, Bayrampaşa

06/2018 - 07/2018

Education

Istanbul University

Computer Programming • Istanbul, Avcılar

07/2018

Anadolu University

Computer Education and Instructional Technologies • Eskişehir, Tepebağ

07/2022

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vue, React, Tailwind CSS, Vuetify, Bootstrap, Vanilla CSS, MSSQL, MySQL, C#, Android Studio(Java), Python

Languages

English, Turkish

Personal Interests

Singing, Football, Computer Games, Volleyball, Swimming

My Websites

https://mertkantecer.vercel.app/

https://upgrademe.vercel.app/